uskype.com 2015-04-28

# Privacy - Appnimi

__Category:[Uncategorised](http://uskype.com/privacy/2-uncategorised) __Created: Monday, 04 August 2014 __Last Updated: Tuesday, 26 August 2014 __Published: Monday, 04 August 2014 __Written by Appnimi

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * For statistical, security or logging purposes certain details such as IP address, geographical, browser details etc are collected mainly through various third party services such as GoogleAnalytics. These details are primarily used to derive traffic trends for the website over the time. It is also used to analyze/detect any attack patterns or hacker activities.
  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

As some softwares to be downloaded use offers from InstallMonetizer.com, please find their Privacy Policy below.

### Privacy:

InstallMonetizer values it’s user’s privacy. They are committed to ethical delivery advertising recommendation and delivery of recommended products. They do not collect any personally identifiable information. In simple language this means, they don’t know the name, gender, age, email, and interests of any users. To read their privacy policy in full, please find it below. In additional, each advertiser product recommended has its own privacy policy which each user can freely review before accepting any recommended product.

### Privacy Policy for InstallMonetizer:

InstallMonetizer herein referred to as (“We” or “InstallMonetizer”) regards each user’s privacy as important. This privacy policy covers the privacy rules associated with user’s interaction with InstallMonetizer’s websites, services or products and recommended advertiser which are presented to end users via other partner software products. User’s must review the partner software product’s own privacy policy and in addition review the privacy policy of any advertiser product recommended by InstallMonetizer. *Partner software product are third party software developers who have chosen to display recommended advertiser software via InstallMonetizer’s platform.

WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY: We collection information to help ensure the products we recommend are compatible with user’s pc specifications. When a user begins installation of a partner software product, Installmonetizer downloads a small file which determines the specifications of a computer, language, software & browsers on the user’s pc, country level location of a user, and verification of any recommended advertiser the user installed. No personally identifiable information is gathered. While visiting our websites, we may send your browser a cookie which is stored in your browser and allows us to identify it. Cookies are used too help better understand our users product interest. In addition, our websites include traffic tracking software which simply tracks the number of visits to our sites and usage of our site. USAGE OF COLLECTED DATA: Any information collect is anonymous. We use the data in whole to improve our advertiser recommendations. We do not sell or otherwise market this information to t hird parties. We may from time to time share with advertisers non-personally identifiable information for them to improve the performance of their products.

We may share information if required to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (3) enforce this Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between you and InstallMonetizer, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of InstallMonetizer, its visitors, users and/or the public.

INFORMATION SECURITY: We use industry standard encryption and security protocols to ensure the data collected is secure. Although no technology is 100% secure we strive to use the best technology to protect our data. That being said, despite the measures we take we cannot warrant the security of any information provided to us. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

If you have feedback, questions or concerns contact us at Privacy, c/o InstallMonetizer 5655 Silver Creek Vly Rd 615 San Jose, CA 95138. You may also email us at mailto:[support@installmonetizer.com](mailto:support@installmonetizer.com)

__Hits: 20486
